weddingclipart.com 2008-03-04

# Privacy Policy

WeddingClipart.com values your privacy. You may contact us any time to learn more about this privacy policy by sending email to [Contact@WeddingClipart.com](mailto:contact@WeddingClipart.com). This Privacy Statement describes how WeddingClipart.com collects and uses information about you when you use the WeddingClipart.com web site ("Site"). 

**Collection and Use of Personal Information by WeddingClipart.com**

With your consent, we collect information that personally identifies you or allows us to contact you when you register to use the Site. Such information may include your name, e-mail address, user identification password and other information (collectively "Personal Information"). You may also provide us with Personal Information in the process of submitting questions and answers while interacting with other members of the Site. WeddingClipart.com uses your Personal Information to operate the Site, to effect your transactions initiated at the Site; to create and share reports about your transactions among themselves. You may correct or update your Personal Information by sending e-mail to [Contact@WeddingClipart.com](mailto:contact@WeddingClipart.com). **

Cookies

**

You must have Cookies turned ON to be a member at WeddingClipart.com. Cookies are very small text files placed on your hard drive by a computer server. It serves as your identification card and is uniquely yours. A cookie can only be read by the server that gave it to you. Cookies tell us that you returned to a specific Web page on our Site, and help us track your preferences. Cookies enable you to login, and help us personalize your experience at the Site by permitting our computer server to "remember" who you are. Some of the advertisers on the Site use cookies to collect similar information, but we do not control the use of cookies by other web site operators or advertisers. **

Personal Information Used for Promotional Purposes

**

We may send you information from time to time about WeddingClipart.com promotional offerings. However, we will not share your Personal Information with any third party without your prior consent. Your consent to receipt of promotional offerings may be indicated in the appropriate check boxes within the Site signifying your preferences. You may be entitled to stop the delivery of promotional information from WeddingClipart.com by using the UNSUBSCRIBE link provided in all marketing emails, or by sending e-mail to [Contact@WeddingClipart.com](mailto:contact@WeddingClipart.com) and, for third party promotional offerings, by contacting the source of that promotional offering. **

Children's Privacy

**

Children under the age of 13 are not allowed to purchase products on the Site. WeddingClipart.com does not knowingly collect Personal Information about child under the age of 13 or allow them to place orders on the Site. If WeddingClipart.com learns that a child under the age of 13 is placing orders on the Site, WeddingClipart.com will close the child's account and delete all information collected about the child. Notwithstanding the foregoing, WeddingClipart.com may choose to retain the child's e-mail address as a means to prevent the child from re-registering with WeddingClipart.com. **

Security

**

We take reasonable steps to protect Personal Information and use technology such as SSL encryption, access control procedures, firewalls and physical security. If you use Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer, SSL displays a "lock" to signify that a page is secure. We urge you to use a password to protect your account from unauthorized access by others. If others, including family or household members, access and use the Site through your password, you are responsible for the actions of those individuals. **

Other Situations in which Personal Information May Be Disclosed

**

We may store and disclose Personal Information allowed or required by applicable law or when deemed advisable by us. This means that we may make disclosures that are necessary or advisable to conform to legal and regulatory requirements or processes and to protect the rights, safety and property of WeddingClipart.com, users of the Site, and the public. **

Changes To The WeddingClipart.com Privacy Statement

**

WeddingClipart.com may make changes to this Privacy Statement from time to time. We will post changes to our privacy statement here, so be sure to check back periodically. We may also notify you of significant changes by e-mail or in other ways. **

Questions, Comments, Concerns

**

If you have any questions or comments about our use of Personal Information, please contact us at [Contact@WeddingClipart.com](mailto:contact@WeddingClipart.com). We will use reasonable efforts to promptly investigate any complaint you may have regarding our use of Personal Information. 

|   | 

**All Suggestions, Billing and Site Questions:** [Contact@WeddingClipart.com](mailto:contact@WeddingClipart.com)

**WeddingClipart.com**  
Letters and Arts, Inc.  
695 Mistletoe Road  
Suite M11  
Ashland, Oregon 97520  
  
---|---|---
